when I was a kid my father had the
biggest car ever made in American
history bigger than a Cadillac a
brand-new 1967 Ford LTD Country Squire
station wagon big car big so big didn't
even have wood paneling on like most
station wagons had two full-grown
redwoods Shep decided now my mother my
father sat up front my brother my sister
my brother they sat in the middle and
their way in the back and I seat their
face in the other direction this is my
chair anywhere we ever went any trip we
ever took this is where I had to sit the
only time I knew where we was going as
we backed out the driveway
are we there yet that's my job
any trip we ever went on - it's my job
every five minutes to ask are we there
yet
no quite asked it how the heck am I
supposed to know I can still see the
house from here now every summer my
father got into his head that we had to
go see America two weeks and every year
go see America get out there the open
roads get out there no super highways
people waving to me all the time now up
there with my brothers and sisters where
they had all sorts of games to play with
coloring books connected bats toys
puzzles all sorts of things to do up
there I was back here with my father's
tools had the makeup things to play with
hey there's a roll of dads good tape boy
I bet I have a lot of fun playing with
that
what are you doing back there you know
we should go to drive-in movie theater a
lot
the whole family me watching Bambi by
Disney I'm watching Bambi and Eddie hey
did you know that Drybar comedy has
their own app download it right now to
watch save share clips and watch my
whole special